Gustav Lindström

+4670 272 39 85 | mail@gustav-lindstrom.se | www.gustav-lindstrom.se



about me

22-year-old Informatics Student at Lund University with a true passion for **tech and business**. Previous experience in Project Management, Development, Data Analysis, and Businessnow looking to **excel in my career**!

People describe me as a hard-working, fast learning, people person. I like to keep myself busy and have, during my academic career, worked several part-time jobs, and explored numerous personal projects.

I also:

- O Have a drivers license.
- o Used to be an elite swimmer at national level.
- o Love hiking, fishing and being outdoors!

visit my website for more work- and academical experience + portfolio!



experience

XLENT Consulting Group Consultant Intern

june 2020 - aug 2020

Planned and developed a "proof of concept" application for the real estate industry. Worked in a SCRUM team with code reviews and version control. Gained a lot of experience in the **software development process**, requirement specification, and cooperating with product owners and managers. Development spanned across the **entire stack**.

Tetra Pak june 2019 - may 2020 Business Intelligence Consultant

Led the development of a new Business Intelligence platform. The project's goal was to improve how the department worked with **big-data** to improve daily workflow and **decision support**. Worked closely with the product owner and played a key role in the launch and promotion of the platform to **support and educate** the users. Job also improved my English in a **business context**. The job started as a summer job and later as a self-employed consultant.

Academic Work / Spago Nanomedical Server Administrator

Responsibility to secure uptime and continuously improve the IT-security within the company's client and server environment. The job has given me a solid understanding of server environments (Windows Server 2016), security, and networking (TCP/IP). Recently I have also been leading a server project for **computations** in python and **CI/CD**. The job started as a consultant and lead to an employment by the company.

Lund Unviersity Lab Supervisor

sep 2020 - present

dec 2018 - present

Tutoring junior students in their computer science assignments. Work involves explaining various concepts and **design patterns** in technologies such as Java, Relational Databases, and C#. Job has improved my ability to make technical concepts comprehensible.

education

Lund University aug 2018 - present BSc. Degree in Informatics

Current education. Learning software development methodologies, system architecture, project management, IT-related law, as well as process and system modeling. Also learning to technically implement languages such as Java (JAVA EE), .NET C#, web technologies, and databases.